&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们谈谈练习的第二部分。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's talk about part two of the exercise.
所以如果我们从这个开始作为我们的解决方案，
So if we're starting from this as our solution,
我们可以开始转换这些常规函数，这些函数是声明或
we can start to convert these regular functions that are declarations or
表达式转换为箭头函数。
expressions into arrow functions.
使用我们知道的关于错误函数语法的各种东西。
Using the various things we know about error functions syntax.
因此，例如，Get Students from ID可以创建为
So for example, get students from ID could be created as
getStudentFromId，它将采取这一点。
getStudentFromId, and it's gonna taken that.
它将返回Student StudentRecords.find()，
And it's going to return the student studentRecords.find(),
这是另一个函数表达式，我们想用箭头函数来做。
and here's another function expression that we wanna do with an arrow function.
以便将其中一个记录下来，且
So that one is record, and
然后这个表情。
then this expression.
这就是我们找到它的方式。
And that's how we find it.
这就是我们对
So, that's our definition for
箭头功能与独立功能相比。
the arrow function as compared to the stand alone function.
我们将对打印记录执行相同的技术。
We'll do the same technique with print records.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：并且不是制作功能块，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And rather than making a function block,
我可以看到这三个函数都是可链接的。
I can actually see that all three of these functions are chainable.
由于排序将保留该数组并且由于该数组将是本地数组，
Since sort will retain the array and since the array will be a local array,
在这种特殊情况下，突变不会有任何影响。
the mutation won't matter in this particular case.
所以我可以通过简单地说
So I can take advantage of that by simply saying
map(GetStudentFromId)，然后我可以说.sort。
recordids.map(getStudentFromId), and then I can say .sort.
在这里，我们有另一个函数，我们应该将它转换为数组函数。
And here, we have another function that we should convert to an array function.
但是这整个if，else，if这件事可以用三元来做，所以
But this whole If, else, if thing can be done as a ternary, so
我们不需要函数体。
we don't need a function body.
所以让我们把它写成接受record1和record2的箭头函数。
So let's write it as the arrow function that takes in record1 and record2.
我们将使用三元，我将把它全部写在一行上，因为为什么不呢。
And we will use a ternary and I will write it all on one line because why not.
那是个玩笑，你应该对此发笑的。
That was a joke, you were supposed to laugh at that.
Record1.name小于Record2.name，则返回-1。
Record1.name is less than Record2.name, then we return -1.
否则(record1.name&gt；record2.name)，
Otherwise (record1.name &gt; record2.name),
我们返回1，否则返回0。
we return 1 otherwise 0.
这就是我们调用排序的错误函数。
So that's our error function that we called the sort on.
最后我们调用.forEach，再一次，
And then finally we call the .forEach, and again,
我们有这个函数，它接收记录并调用控制台日志。
we have this Function which is receiving a record and calling console log.
由于控制台日志是函数调用，
Since console log is a function call,
它适合作为表达式，这意味着我们不需要箭头函数体。
it's suitable as an expression which means we don't need an arrow function body.
所以我们可以简单地说记录，然后调用console.log，
So we can simply say record and then call the console.log,
而且，因为我很懒，我只是复制它。
and, since I'm lazy, I'm just gonna copy it.
我不想再打一遍。
I don't wanna retype it.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是我们的箭头函数表示的打印记录。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And there is our arrow function representation of print records.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：付费学生注册&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：it
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Paid students to enroll &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It
不会收到任何东西，所以它是一个箭头函数。
doesn't receive anything, so it's an arrow function.
同样，我可以看到我最终要做的是返回一个数组。
And again, I can see that what I'm ultimately doing is returning an array.
所以我只需返回数组，然后
So I can just simply return that array, and then have
包括在数组中，通过链接将会发生什么。
Included in the array what's going to happen through chaining.
所以，我要展开这个表达式。
So, that and I'm going to spread out this expression.
这个表达式将以StudentRecords.filter和
And this expression will start with studentRecords.filter and
这里我们使用另一个在线函数表达式，它可以是箭头函数。
here we are with another online function expression that can be arrow function.
所以我会写一个箭头函数。
So I'll write an arrow function.
因为我很懒，所以我要把它复制下来。
Takes in record and since I'm being lazy, I'm gonna copy that.
这就是我们的箭头功能。
There's our arrow function.
过滤后，我们可以简单地调用网点图，直接改变它。
After filter, we can simply call the dot map, change directly off of it.
我们还有另一个内联函数，名为“get Student I-D”。
We have another inline function called, "Get student I-D".
它只是返回记录。
It simply returns record.
这是每个人最喜欢的箭头功能，它就是这样做的。
This is everybody's favorite arrow function which just does that.
然后阵列被展开。
And that array then gets spread out.
这是一个被分散开来的i-d列表
It's a list of I-Ds that gets spread out
进入这个数组，这个数组是由付费学生返回注册的。
into this array that's returned from paid students to enroll.
这就是我们的箭头函数。
So there is our arrow function.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在，最后，提醒未付是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And now, finally, remind unpaid is
一个箭头函数，它接受记录ID和
an arrow function that takes record IDs and
它做了recordIds.filter，并且
it Does recordIds.filter, and
我们有学生ID箭头功能或
we have a student ID arrow function or
传入的名为StudentId的参数。
parameter called studentId that comes in.
我们可以再一次
And we can, again,
通过对函数调用执行属性链来避免需要箭头块。
avoid needing an arrow block by doing a property chain off the function call.
所以我们可以简单地说，getStudentFromId(StudentId)，
So we can simply say, getStudentFromId(studentId),
然后访问该调用的属性，并否定它。
and then access the property off of that call, and negate it.
然后，我们可以使用该输入调用printRecords&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：。
And then, we can call printRecords &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: With that input.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这就是箭头函数，耶！
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there is that arrow function, and yay!
没有更多的常规函数，只有箭头函数。
No more regular functions, only arrow functions.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：关于练习的第二部分有什么问题吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Any questions about part two of the exercise?
凯尔·辛普森：什么事？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：有一段时间使用多重三元作为回调函数，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: There was a moment with the multiple ternary as the callback function,
链式数组方法，就像-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，
the chained array method, it's like- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah,
我把所有[CROSSTALK]&gt；&gt；扬声器1：我就像，
the one that I put all [CROSSTALK] &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: I was like,
当然，这只是他在内心创造的一种修辞姿态。
surely that's just a rhetorical gesture that he created inside.
然后我意识到，我两周前就写了类似的东西。
Then I realized, I had written something like it two weeks ago.
我就像，上帝。
I was like, God.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我知道，我对那些喜欢
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I know, my observation of those that like to
写箭头的功能是有一种倾向
write arrow functions is that there is a predisposition
为了使用最简洁的语法，
to use the most concise syntax possible,
尽你所能使用任何技巧。
using whatever tricks you possibly can.
包括嵌套在一起的内联三元组，
Including Inline ternaries that are nested together,
使用逗号运算符嵌套表达式。
using the comma operator to nest expressions.
我见过人们在箭头中定义参数
I've seen people define parameters in the arrow
参数列表是未使用的变量，因此
parameter list that are unused variables so
他们不需要声明一个变量来在他们的表达式中使用。
that they don't have to declare a variable to use inside of their expression.
我的意思是，任何类型的句法技巧，你都可以用来把它简化成一个简明的箭头
I mean, any sort of syntactic trick you can use to get it down to a concise arrow
表达似乎是常态。
expression seems to be the norm.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，所以希望你现在感觉更好一点
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so hopefully you now feel a little bit more with
一些稍微真实的世俗代码。
some slightly more real worldish code.
关于我们可以创建为的函数之间的差异的一些想法
Some idea about the differences between the functions that we can create as
声明，作为内联函数表达式，以及
declarations, as inline function expressions, and
现在甚至作为箭头函数表达式。
now even as arrow function expressions.
你可以做一些并排的比较。
You have some side by side comparison that you can make.
对这些样式是否更具可读性做出自己的决定，
Make your own determinations on whether or not these styles are more readable,
或者更易于维护，为您的目的。
or more maintainable, for your purpose.